let data;
export default data = [
  {
    question: "How do you say 'Hello' in Japanese?",
    options: ["Konnichiwa", "Hajimemashite", "Yoroshiku onegaishimasu", "Eigo o hanashimasu ka?"],
    correct_option: "Konnichiwa"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the Japanese phrase for 'Nice to meet you'?",
    options: ["Konnichiwa", "Hajimemashite", "Yoroshiku onegaishimasu", "Eigo o hanashimasu ka?"],
    correct_option: "Hajimemashite"
  },
  {
    question: "How would you ask 'Do you speak English?' in Japanese?",
    options: ["Konnichiwa", "Hajimemashite", "Yoroshiku onegaishimasu", "Eigo o hanashimasu ka?"],
    correct_option: "Eigo o hanashimasu ka?"
  },
  {
    question: "What does 'Kore wa nan desu ka?' mean in English?",
    options: ["What is your name?", "How much does this cost?", "Can you please help me?", "What is this?"],
    correct_option: "What is this?"
  },
  {
    question: "How would you ask 'Can you please help me?' in Japanese?",
    options: ["Konnichiwa", "Hajimemashite", "Yoroshiku onegaishimasu", "Tasukete moraemasuka?"],
    correct_option: "Tasukete moraemasuka?"
  },
  {
    question: "What does 'Yoroshiku onegaishimasu' mean in English?",
    options: ["Hello", "Nice to meet you", "Please treat me favorably", "Do you speak English?"],
    correct_option: "Please treat me favorably"
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say 'Nice to meet you' in Japanese?",
    options: ["Konnichiwa", "Hajimemashite", "Yoroshiku onegaishimasu", "Eigo o hanashimasu ka?"],
    correct_option: "Hajimemashite"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the English translation of 'Eigo o hanashimasu ka?'?",
    options: ["Do you speak English?", "How much does this cost?", "Can you please help me?", "What is your name?"],
    correct_option: "Do you speak English?"
  },
  {
    question: "How do you greet someone with 'Hello' in Japanese?",
    options: ["Konnichiwa", "Hajimemashite", "Yoroshiku onegaishimasu", "Tasukete moraemasuka?"],
    correct_option: "Konnichiwa"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the Japanese phrase for 'How much does this cost?'?",
    options: ["Konnichiwa", "Hajimemashite", "Yoroshiku onegaishimasu", "Kore wa ikura desu ka?"],
    correct_option: "Kore wa ikura desu ka?"
  }
]
